[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":262521,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":266923,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":4684,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":271610,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5990,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":277602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1158,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":278761,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2719,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":281482,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1038,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":282522,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the secon d one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":6152,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":288674,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":943,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":289618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2527,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":292146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":823,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":292970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":295890,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6< /sub> 0  = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":695,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":296586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2095,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":298683,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":724,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":299409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br  /> (Rem ember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":301513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":920,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":302434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.) ","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3327,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":305761,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":727,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":306489,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2336,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":308826,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":958,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":309785,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2407,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":312193,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":582,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":312776,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":13446,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":326226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse und er +<sub >6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":22583,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":348810,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"8","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["8"],"rt":10039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":358849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":6144,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":364994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</ sub>? <b r /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5653,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":370649,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":10191,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":380841,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2614,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":383456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2600,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":386057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":1815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":387873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 =  0, and 0  is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":775,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":388649,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4327,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":392977,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":734,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":393713,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation  can sim ply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":7313,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":401026,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<s ub>6</su b> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":66559,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":467585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":471153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":6463,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":477617,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under  +<sub>6< /sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2855,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":480473,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1277,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":481753,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under + <sub>6</ sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":1815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":483569,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1319,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":484889,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":491032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":2440,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":493473,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice q uestion  with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":39390,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":532864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4128,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":536993,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1071,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":538064,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3054,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":541120,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":544328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3015,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":547344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":2158,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":549504,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":553616,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":7639,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":561256,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4 + 1 = 5, and since it is less than 9 we do not subtract 9","explanation_history":["4 + 1 = 5, and since it is less than 9 we do not subs","4 + 1 = 5, and since it is less than 9 we do not subtrat ","4 + 1 = 5, and since it is less than 9 we do not subtrat","4 + 1 = 5, and since it is less than 9 we do not subtract 9"],"response_history":["5"],"rt":18126,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":579384,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8+4 = 12, and because it is more than 9 we subtract 9 and get 3","explanation_history":["8+4 = 12, and bceau","8+4 =  12, and bcea","8+4 = 12, and bce","8+4 = 12, and bc","8+4 = 12, and becaus ","8+4 = 12, and because it is more than 9 we subr","8+4 = 12, and because it is more than 9 we subtract 9 and get 3"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":71694,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":651080,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"This is the identity because if we add anything to 0 the answer is that number","explanation_history":["Ti","This is the identity because if we add anything to 0 i","This is the identity because if we add anything to 0 the anse","This is the identity because if we add anything to 0 the answer is still 9","This is the identity because if we add anything to 0 the answer is still 0","This is the identity because if we add  anything  to 0 the answer s","This is the identity because if we add anything to 0 the answer is that numbver","This is the identity because if we add anything to 0 the answer is that numbve","This is the identity because if we add anything to 0 the answer is that numbv","This is the identity because if we add anything to 0 the answer is that number"],"response_history":["The identity u","0"],"rt":57358,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":708439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"I think it is 5?","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I think it is 5?"],"rt":7431,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":715871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"2?","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2?"],"rt":3402,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":719276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":721827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"The inverse of 3 is 3?","explain":true,"explanation":"I had a tough time understanding this concept, I admit I am guessing here","explanation_history":["I had a touch","I had a touc","I h ad a tou gh tu","I had a tough time understanding this concept, I admit","I had a tough time understanding this concept, I admit I am guesi","I had a tough time understanding this concept, I admit I am guessing here"],"response_history":["The inver ","The inverse of 3 is 3?"],"rt":25852,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":747680,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Again, I wasn't as clear on this meaning. This is totally a guess. Sorry!!","explanation_history":["Again, I wasn't as clean","Again, I wasn't as clear on this meaning. This is totally a guess. Sorry!!"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":18486,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":766168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"I am guessing, I do not understand the concept of a generator.","explanation_history":["I had a tough time understanding this concept, I admit I am guessing here","I am guessing, I do not know","I am guessing, I do not kno","I am guessing, I do not kn","I am guessing, I do not k","I am guessing, I do not understand the concept of a generator."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":49486,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":815655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"Another guess. I just don't understand th at conce pt.","explanation_history":["Another guess. I just don't undre","Another guess. I just don't undr","Another guess. I just don't understand that concept."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":13063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":828719,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"Another guess. The concept is not solid for me.","explanation_history":["Another guess. The concept is not solid for me."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":10935,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":839655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other  countin g number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":15286,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":854943,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+0=1?","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1+0=1?"],"rt":21439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":876383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I have no idea","explain":true,"explanation":"This doesn't make sense to me, I am sorry.","explanation_history":["This doesnt ","This doesnt","This doesn't make sense to me, I am sorry."],"response_history":["I have no idea"],"rt":13149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":889535,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know, I am sorry","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I don't know, I am sorry"],"rt":42482,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":932018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":3563,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":935582,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":3789,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":939374,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":2735,"trial_type":" question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":942111,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"I am seriously just guessing. If I was better at math, I would have gone to med school instead of law school.","explanation_history":["I am seriouls","I am serioul","I am seriously g","I am seriously just guessing. If I was better at math, I would have gone to g","I am seriously just guessing. If I was better at math, I would have gone to med school instead of lw","I am seriously just guessing. If I was better at math, I would have gone to med school instead of law school."],"response_history":["True"],"rt":49868,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":991982,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":4093,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":996078,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"I am totally guessing.","explanation_history":["I am totally guessing."],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":6311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1002390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":2423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1004814,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1526,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1006342,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"35","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["35"],"rt":2127,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1008470,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Doctorate, M.D., etc.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"rt":2767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1011237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra, Geometry, Statistics","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Algebra, Geometry, Stat","Algebra, Geometry, Statistics"],"rt":10336,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1021574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1024678,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":3007,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1027686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1029790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do y ou feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat"],"rt":3222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1033014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2880,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1035894,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":1558,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1037454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Engl","English"],"rt":4237,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1041694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3943,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1045638,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have done well in higher mathematics, but I am seriously questioning whether that was true after this experience. That being said, thanks for the opportunity to participate and best of luck with your research!","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have fdo","This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have fd","This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have f","This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have done ","This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have done well in higher mathematics, but I am seriously questioning whether that was true after this experience. That being said, thanks for the opportunbi","This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have done well in higher mathematic s, but I  am seriously questioning whether that was true after this experience. That being said, thanks for the opportunb","This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have done well in higher mathematics, but I am seriously questioning whether that was true after this experience. That being said, thanks for the opportunity ti p","This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have done well in higher mathematics, but I am seriously questioning whether that was true after this experience. That being said, thanks for the opportunity ti ","This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have done well in higher mathematics, but I am seriously questioning whether that was true after this experience. That being said, thanks for the opportunity tio","This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have done well in higher mathematics, but I am seriously questioning whether that was true after this experience. That being said, thanks for the opportunity ti","This was so hard for me! I was  always  told I'd have done well in higher mathematics, but I am seriously questioning whether that was true after this experience. That being said, thanks for the opportunity to participate and best of luci","This was so hard for me! I was always told I'd have done well in higher mathematics, but I am seriously questioning whether that was true after this experience. That being said, thanks for the opportunity to participate and best of luck with your research!"],"rt":36456,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1082094,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]